Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/lindsay-robinson-23bb4510 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Event Planning
Non-profits
Political Campaigns

Lindsay Robinson

Director of Development at Multidisciplinary Association for Psychedelic Studies (MAPS)

United States

Summary

20+ year fundraising professional with senior management and leadership expertise in cannabis policy reform, state and federal policy and advocacy, fundraising, strategic planning, and budget development and oversight.

In my current role as Director of Development at the Multidisciplinary Association of Psychedelic Studies (MAPS), I'm honored to lead a team of brilliant fundraising professionals. At MAPS, we believe psychedelics are powerful tools for healing the psyche. For the past 37 years, our clinical trials have shown the benefits and potential of psychedelics in hopes to rewrite their cultural context. It's our mission to create a world where psychedelics and cannabis become available for safe, legal, and beneficial uses, and governed by rigorous scientific evaluation.

As the former executive director of California's largest and most influential cannabis trade association (CCIA), I worked on policy reform which benefited legal cannabis businesses across the state. CCIA has led the charge on some of the most comprehensive cannabis reforms policies in California. Through our lobbying efforts, I worked closely with the regulatory agencies governing cannabis, as well as state legislators and the Newsom Administration.

Prior to working with CCIA, I served as Director of Development at the Marijuana Policy Project for nearly a decade. My passion for drug policy reform and fundraising has helped usher in dozens of statewide efforts which have transformed the legal landscape of cannabis in the United States. I am extremely proud to have contributed to the fundamental shift of how we regulate cannabis.

I am a graduate of the University of San Francisco's Master of Nonprofit Administration program with a focus in Development. I have worked in the nonprofit sector for over 20 years.

Experience

Multidisciplinary Association for Psychedelic Studies (MAPS)
Director of Development at Multidisciplinary Association for Psychedelic Studies (MAPS)

May 2023 - Present (7 months)

Founded in 1986, the Multidisciplinary Association for Psychedelic Studies (MAPS) is a 501(c)(3) non-profit research and educational organization that develops medical, legal, and cultural contexts for people to benefit from the careful uses of psychedelics and marijuana.

We further our mission by:

- Developing psychedelics and marijuana into prescription medicines
- Training therapists and working to establish a network of treatment centers
- Supporting scientific research into spirituality, creativity, and neuroscience
- Educating the public honestly about the risks and benefits of psychedelics and marijuana

California Cannabis Industry Association 7 years 5 months

Executive Director May 2017 - May 2023 (6 years 1 month) Sacramento, California Area

Member Board Of Directors January 2016 - May 2017 (1 year 5 months) Sacramento, California Area

Marijuana Policy Project
Director of Development
December 2013 - May 2017 (3 years 6 months)
San Francisco Bay Area

San Francisco and Marin Food Banks Senior Manager, Major Gifts December 2012 - December 2013 (1 year 1 month)

Marijuana Policy Project Development Officer March 2008 - December 2012 (4 years 10 months)

Center for Justice and Accountability Development and Outreach Associate January 2006 - March 2008 (2 years 3 months) San Francisco Bay Area

Education

University of San Francisco
Masters, Nonprofit Administration · (2006 - 2008)

University of Vermont
Bachelors, Environmental Studies · (1995 - 1999)